（忆往昔）
查理 她在通过她的化名给托皮卡的
Charlie … she's been making donations through her aliases.
肖尼郡综合医院捐款
to Shawnee County General here in Topeka.
做好事吗
Like, a charity?
给一个病人 叫格特鲁德·米德尔顿
A patient. Gertrude middleton.
她和丈夫被酒驾司机撞到了
She and her husband were hit by a drunk driver.
我当时在外面过夜 我害怕了
I was at a sleepover, and I got scared.
我打给我爸妈让他们来接我
I called my parents to come and get me.
他们那晚本不该开车出门的
They should never have been driving that night.
这东西必须得去掉
This thing has got to go.
要去除其效力需要很强大的力量
It will take a very powerful force to remove the effect.
那就把它烧掉 我不要这么活着
Well, then burn it off! I'm not living like this.
该隐仍然有血印 对吗
Cain still has the Mark, right?
他一直带着它
So he's lived with it.
也许你有一部分
Maybe there's a part of you.
想要向它投降
that wants to give in to it,
也许你得与之斗争
and maybe you have to fight that.
那一部分强大的力量得是你
Part of that powerful force has to be you.
拯救他人 降妖除魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, the family business?
这我懂
I am down.
但是 我的任务呢
But… Where's my quest?
是通往奥兹国的钥匙
It's the key to Oz.
有很多神奇的方法可以进入奥兹国
There are magical ways into Oz …
这把钥匙能把任何一扇关着的门
This key will turn any locked door.
变成前往奥兹国的传送门
into a portal to Oz.
- 你来不来啊 - 去奥兹国吗
- You coming or what? - To Oz?
对 你说想要来一场历险
Yeah. You said you were looking for adventure.
机会来了 小红毛
Well, here it is, red.
（如今）
求你
Please…
我别的都不知道了
I-I don't know anything else.
我知道 我还是要折磨你
I know. I'm gonna torture you anyway.
谁不喜欢折磨人呢
'Cause who doesn't love a little torture?
[邪恶力量 第10季第11集]
好 随时告诉我消息
All right, well, just… just keep me posted, okay?
嗯 好嘞
Yeah, you got it.
等等 小卡 还在吗
Wait, Cass. You there?
谢了 嗯
Hey, thanks. Yeah.
你做了蛋白蛋饼吗
You made egg-white omelettes?
嗯 最棒的早餐
Yeah. Breakfast of Champions…
对你这样的书呆子而言
you know, if you're a dork like you.
- 而且你今天一直睡到7点 - 是啊
- And you slept past 7:00? - Yeah, well,
直到我们查明该隐血印的去除方法
until we get answers on this Mark of Cain,
我要12步修身养性 避免堕落
I am on a 12-step program not to backslide.
- 12步修身养性 - 对
- 12 steps? - Yeah.
如果该隐能做到带着血印生活而不被黑化
Hey, if Cain found a way to live with it after going dark side,
那我也得想办法克制冲动
then I just got to find a way to keep it in check,
所以 我这一周都没喝酒了
so haven't had a drink in a week,
每晚睡8小时
eight hours of rack time every night,
还有这道杰作
and…now this masterpiece.
这才三步
That's three steps.
闭嘴吃你的
Shut up and eat.
做得好棒啊
Wow. That's… that's awesome.
烂死了
It's crap.
天呐
Ugh. God.
等我一去掉这个恶魔荡妇纹身
Soon as we get rid of this demonic tramp stamp,
我就要回归饮酒 吃汉堡 再饮酒的生活
I am back on the booze, burgers, and…more booze.
告诉我你有发现
Tell me you got something.
搞什么
What the hell?
该隐还是克劳力
Cain or Crowley?
查理
Charlie.
她从奥兹回来了吗 居然没打电话
Is she back from Oz? She didn't call?
嗯
Yeah, uh…
她很忙啊
She's been busy.
这是什么啊
What the hell am I looking at?
我在查阅新闻
So, you know, I was looking into the news,
找有什么古怪
checking for anything weird, right?
发现了一则关于一男子被折磨的新闻
I found this story about a torture vic.
他邻居家的小孩
Apparently, some kid videotaped this.
拍下了这一幕
at his next-door neighbor's house.
你说什么 查理折磨了别人
What are you saying, Charlie tortured someone?
我们那个查理吗
Our Charlie?
小不点 连霍比特人都不忍伤害
Yea high, wouldn't hurt a Hobbit,
呆萌可爱的那个
practically sparkles?
（本地地检官遭人折磨）
查理 接电话啊
Come on, Charlie, pick up.
那个被她折磨的人
The guy she went all Jack Bauer on…
叫彼得·哈珀
uh, Peter Harper.
她不接
She's not answering.
是托皮卡的地检官
District attorney in Topeka.
根据文章所述
According to this article,
他不是当地唯一遇袭的人
he wasn't the only person in town that was hit.
前一晚 一名法庭速记员遭到了袭击
Uh, a court stenographer was assaulted the night before.
查理绝不会无缘无故袭击人的
Well, you know, Charlie wouldn't go off on someone without a reason.
我也这么认为
Yeah, I wouldn't think so either,
- 但你看那段视频啊 - 我看了
- but look at the video. - Oh, I'm looking at it.
但我们的所作所为 如果不明真相
But you know what we do, taken out of context,
看上去也会这么糟糕
it doesn't look that much different.
她或许在猎魔
She could be hunting.
我们去跟这混蛋谈谈 看看怎么回事吧
Why don't we go talk to this asshat and see what's going on?
好了吗
Hey, ready?
- 嗯 我们上路吧 - 我们走
- Yeah. Yeah, let's do this. - Let's go.
袭击发生前 你发现什么怪事了吗
Now, did you notice anything odd before the attack…
怪味儿 异响
any, uh, strange smells, weird noises?
没有
No, no, nothing.
我就是在家 准备上床
I was just at home here, getting ready for bed,
那个疯婆子就袭击了我
and that crazy bitch jumped me.
她只想打听一桩
All she wanted was to know was about some case.
我多年前的案子
that I worked on years ago…
醉驾司机拦腰撞上另一辆车
drunk driver T-boned another car,
撞死司机
killing the driver,
副驾被当场宣布脑死亡
and the passenger was declared brain-dead on the scene.
米德尔顿夫妇
The Middletons.
他们有个12岁的女儿
They had a daughter, 12 years old.
他们当时正开车去接她
They were on their way to pick her up.
没错 你怎么知道
Yeah, that's right. How did you know that?
我们联调局会调查
Well, we do our homework at the FBI.
那你就该知道 那案子根本没上过法庭
Okay, well, then you know the case never went to trial.
我连证据都没见着 案子就被撤下了
Before I could even see the evidence, it was off the books.
案卷全部封存了
All the files were sealed.
这怎么可能呢
Now, how is that even possible?
不知道
I don't know.
但我今早又查了
But I looked into it this morning.
那宗案子的记录哪都找不到
There's no record of that case anywhere,
施行逮捕的警官此后也已过世
and the arresting officer has since passed away.
什么都没有了 除了这个
There's nothing, except for this…
米德尔顿女孩的社保档案
the social service file on the Middletons' kid.
老实说 没什么用处
It's not very helpful, to be honest with you.
那孩子早失踪了
The kid has disappeared,
直到现在
until now.
关于案子 你还记得其他任何事吗
Now, is there anything else you can remember about the case…
- 任何人 - 没了
- any names you can think of? - No.
我跟警察也说了 那是很久以前了
Like I told the police, it was so long ago.
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
好吧
All right.
是这样的
Here's the thing.
我们过来的时候 去找了另一位受害人
We talked to the other victim on the way here…
那个速记员
the stenographer.
她说袭击者直到她给出了一个名字
Now, she said the attacker didn't let her go.
才肯放她走
until she gave up a name…
你的名字
your name.
好吧
Okay.
那这跟我在我家中
But w-what does that have to do.
遭袭有什么关系
with m-me being attacked in my own home, here?
你给出了谁的名字
What name did you give up?
我跟警察说的话 我都告诉你们了
Look, I told you everything I told the police.
这女人闯进来 把我打得半死
This woman comes in here, beats the tar out of me,
但我已经没什么人可以供出了
but… but there's no name to give up,
所以我也不知道该…
so I-I don't know what else to…
你干什么
Hey, w-what are you doing?!
老实交待 你个混蛋
Talk, you son of a bitch!
我才是受害的一方啊
Hey, look, I'm the victim, here!
交待
Talk!
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
好吧
All right.
我说
案卷被封之后
After the files were sealed…
我去问过
I pushed.
然后
And, uh…
他们给了我不少钱
They offered me money… a lot of money.
说名字
Give me a name.
那些钱一直是从海外账户汇来
The money kept on coming in from overseas accounts.
- 说名字 - 我会被取消律师资格的
- Give me a name! - I will be disbarred!
那是你最不该担心的事了
That'll be the least of your worries,
我保证
I promise you that.
芭芭拉·科迪议员
Councilwoman Barbara Cordry.
西莱斯特·米德尔顿
Celeste Middleton.
西莱斯特 那是查理的真名
Celeste… that's Charlie's real name.
看来她是在找害她家毁人亡的人
Guess she's looking for the person who, uh, destroyed her family.
你能怪她吗
Can you blame her?
我们得找到她
You know, we just got to find her.
免得她做什么没法回头的事
before she does something nobody can walk away from.
芭芭拉·科迪
Barbara Cordry?
有事吗
Can I help you?
是的 我是盖布利尔特别探员
Yes. I'm Special Agent Gabriel.
这位是我搭档 科林斯特别探员
This is my partner, Special Agent Collins.
能进去吗
May we come in?
- 什么事啊 - 我们有几个
- What's this about? - We have some questions.
关于一起多年前的醉驾事故案子的问题
about a drunk-driving case from a while back.
当事人是米德尔顿夫妇
involving the Middleton family.
我不知道你们在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
- 女士 可否… - 抱歉
- Ma'am, if we could just… - Sorry.
我还在休假
I'm still on vacation.
请跟我的助手定个预约吧
Feel free to schedule an appointment with my assistant.
她会为你们安排的
She'll pencil you both in.
- 有问题 - 是啊
- Guilty much? - Yeah.
甘蓝是什么鬼啊
What the hell is kale?
「反权威
"Anti-authority disorder,
临床抑郁 暴力发作「
clinical depression, violent outbursts."
- 查理真是… - 伙计
- Charlie was, uh… - Dude.
如果我们那个年纪被心理医生审核了
If a shrink interviewed us at that age,
结果难道会是温馨美好的吗
you think the report would be all kittens and rainbows?
拜托
Come on.
她是个好姑娘
She's a good kid.
这一切肯定是有原因的
There's got to be an explanation for this, man.
肯定是的
There's just got to be.
就该知道火箭和格鲁特会找到我
Should have known Rocket and Groot would track me down.
放了她
Let her go.
谁
Who?
她吗
Oh, her?
- 别这样 - 我只想要答案
- Don't do this. - I just want answers.
是吗 你什么开始为找答案伤人了
Yeah? Since when do you start pounding on people for those?
你在奥兹遇到了什么啊
What the hell happened to you in Oz?
我想要的一切
Everything I wanted.
冒险
An adventure.
还弄到一把短剑
Even got my own little sword.
查理
Charlie…
萨姆 你真可爱
Oh, Sam, you're adorable.
但你不会伤害我
You're not gonna hurt me.
事实上 你的问题就在这儿
In fact, that's your problem…
总那么有原则 从不伤人
all good-guy code, no bite.
真是浪费
What a waste.
你呢
And you…
总是让他拖累你
Always letting this albatross hold you back.
好吧 告诉你
Okay, all right, you know what?
我不知道这是什么情况
I don't know what's going on here, okay?
但你不是这样的人
But this… this is not you.
我就是这样
Oh, it's me, all right.
查理 把刀放下 放她走
Charlie, put the knife down. Let her go.
我们不想伤害你 丫头
We don't want to hurt you, kiddo,
但我们不会让你这么做的
but we're not gonna let you do this.
够了
Stop!
该死
Crap!
萨姆
Sam!
- 你没事吧 - 嗯
- You all right? - Yeah.
- 她跟你说什么了 - 她就是…
- What did she say to you? - She… she just…
她要银行对账单
she wanted the bank statements.
查理
Charlie! Hey!
你个混蛋丫头
Oh, you son of a bitch.
你们好啊
What's up, bitches?
好吧
Right.
我得跟你们说说情况
Um we should probably catch up.
有两个你 一个好 一个坏
There two of you… one good, one…bad?
忍者混蛋版的你吗
Yeah, what, dick you is some sort of a ninja?
她的确很厉害
She is a badass, yeah.
好吧 等等 倒回去
O-okay. Hold on. Back up.
桃乐西 奥兹 黄砖路 这我们都知道
We were there for Dorothy, Oz, yellow brick road.
后来呢
B-but then…
战争
War.
翡翠城之战
The war for Emerald City.
很酷炫
It was awesome.
但后来就不酷炫了
Until not so much.
我们要输了
We were gonna lose,
于是我做了个交易 跟…
so I made a deal with the wizard…
奥兹的巫师
of Oz.
兜帽加恐怖面具
Wears a hood and a creepy mask,
挺混蛋 好愉快啊
kind of a jerk… good times.
他说我们如果想赢
He said for us to win,
我得释放内心真正的阴暗面
I had to unleash my true darkness,
不是比喻哦
which he meant literally.
他用了奥兹的内心钥
He used the inner key of Oz.
开启了灵魂之门 把阴暗面放出来了
It opens a door to your soul and lets the darkness out.
我们的身体还有联系
Uh, we're still connected physically.
如果你们伤害她 也会伤到我
If you hurt her, you hurt me.
但总之 她是坏人 我是好人
But bottom line, she's bad, and I'm good.
告诉你们
And let me just tell you,
做好人 真是烦人
being good is really annoying.
一般在这种地方
Normally in a place like this,
我会大肆饮酒
I'd be pounding Harvey Wallbangers.
看酒保美臀了
and checking out the bartender's ass.
但我现在只想喝苏打水
Now all I want to do is sip club soda.
送她去上大学
and send her to college.
好吧 好查理
Okay, uh…good Charlie.
那么黑暗查理为什么一心复仇
So, why is dark Charlie gunning for revenge?
她是想赢回我的心
She's trying to win me back.
黑暗查理一个人就赢下了战争
Dark Charlie won the war single-handedly.
但是
But…
她做了些很糟糕的事
She did some truly awful things.
我告诉她
But I told her.
我再也不想靠近她了
I didn't want any part of her near me again, ever.
她去找那些…
Going after the person who mur… mur… uh…
夺走我父母的人
who took my parents away.
是她表明我们有多亲密的变态方式
is her messed-up way of showing me how close we are,
或者说她认为我们可以多亲密
or… or could be.
我一直说「她」 但她就是我
I keep calling her "she, " but she's me.
是我做了这些事
I'm the one doing this.
查理 那不是你
Charlie, that… that's not who you are, okay?
那只是一个变态版本的
It's… it's a twisted version of…
我
Me.
我一直在跟踪她
I've been following her.
想趁她干下蠢事前拦下她
so I can catch her before she does something stupid.
然后永远把她关起来
a-and just lock her away forever.
查理
Uh, Charlie…
这不是办法
That's not an answer.
萨姆说得对
Sam's right.
我们得回奥兹去
We'll go back to Oz,
去混蛋巫师那里拿钥匙
and we'll… we'll get the key from the wizard of douche,
然后把你们拼回去
and we'll put you back together.
就算我想要跟她合并
Even if I did want her back…
看啊
Look.
黑暗的我弄坏了钥匙
dark me broke the key.
我们没办法去找巫师了
There's no way to get back to the wizard.
一步步来
Okay, okay, first thing's first.
我们得先找到黑暗查理
We need to find dark Charlie.
赶在她找到醉驾司机之前
before she finds the drunk driver.
我们知道芭芭拉给出了她当年的银行账单
So, we know Barbara gave up her old bank statements, right?
那么黑暗查理大概会追随资金
That means dark Charlie will probably follow the money.
找当初付钱的人
back to whoever made the payoffs.
我就会这么做
That's what I would do.
好吧
All right.
我再去续一杯
I'll get some refills.
我们需要你
We need you…
黑入芭芭拉的银行账户
to hack into Barbara's bank accounts.
不行
I can't.
- 什么 - 那样太坏了
- What? - It's bad.
- 我说了 做好人很烦人的 - 这样呢
- I told you… being good is annoying. - How about this…
你教教我怎么做 行吗
how about you guide me through the process,
这样使坏的就是我了
and then I'm the bad one?
好了 芭芭拉的钱都来自海外账户
Okay, so, Barbara's payments all came from offshore accounts,
用傀儡公司掩盖来源
which were routed through dummy corporations,
而这些公司都破产了
which have all gone belly-up.
直接跳到最后 龙纹身的男孩
All right, skip to the end, dragon tattoo.
最终都查到这人身上吗
They all lead back to this guy?
罗素·惠灵顿
Russell Wellington.
根据他的个人档案看
And according to his personal records,
事故一周后
he had a-a car that was reported stolen.
他报失了一辆车
the… the week of the accident,
这辆车一直没被找到
a-a car that was never recovered.
在所谓的「盗车」发生之后
And after the supposed "theft, "
他去休假了两周
he went on a sabbatical from work for two weeks.
回到公司的时候 身上有淤青 脚踝也伤了
and returned to work with bruises and a broken ankle.
那就是他了
So this is him.
就是这人…
This is the man who, uh…
别看了
And you're done.
萨姆
Sam.
伙计们
Hey, dudes. Dudes.
秘密不是好事
Secrets are bad.
查理 我觉得你不该靠近
Charlie, I don't think you should be anywhere around.
这个人渣推销员
this piece-of-crap salesman.
而且我觉得找到黑暗查理
And… and I don't think that finding dark Charlie.
把她关起来不能解决问题
and locking her up is gonna work.
她虽然黑暗
I mean, she may be…dark,
但她始终是你的一部分
but she's still a part of you.
你说得对
You're right.
虽不中听 但是对的
I hate it, but you're right.
好吧 我们去地堡吧
Okay. Let's go to the bunker.
鲍姆用钥匙去了奥兹
Baum used the key to Oz.
或许记录者的档案里有关于钥匙的记录
Maybe there's something in the Men of Letters' files about the key.
如果我们修好钥匙 就能回奥兹
If we fix it, we can get back to Oz.
嗯 你们去弄那个
All right, you guys dig into that.
我去盯着罗素
I'm gonna keep an eye on Russell.
等着黑暗查理找上门
and, uh…wait for dark Charlie to show up.
这样好吗
Are you sure?
迪恩 或许该由我来…
Dean, maybe… maybe I should be the one…
不不 我行的
No, no, no, no, no. I got. It's, uh…
真难以置信我还得…
I just can't believe I have to…
保护那个人渣
protect this piece of crap.
你得保护他们两个人
No, you got to protect them both.
如果黑暗查理受伤了 那…
I mean, if dark Charlie gets hurt, then…
我也遭殃 小心哦
So do I, so…be careful.
知道了
Got it.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
路上跟你说 走吧
I'll tell you on the way. Come on.
平静思绪的关键
The key to quieting your mind.
就是专心于平静
is minding your quiet.
知道并了解 缺乏答案…
Know and understand … the lack of an answer is …
（罗素·惠灵顿）
（惠灵顿地产开发）
好 找到了 克莱夫·狄龙
Okay, here we go. Clive Dillon.
他是第一个发现通往奥兹国钥匙的记录者
He is the Man of Letters that first discovered the key to Oz.
根据这个事故报告
So, according to this incident report,
克莱夫去了奥兹国 但是把钥匙留在了人间
Clive went to Oz, but he left the key on earth,
然后李曼·弗兰克·鲍姆发现了钥匙
and then L. Frank Baum found the key.
去奥兹国救克莱夫
and went to rescue Clive in Oz.
桃乐西就是那时候偷偷溜进去
That's when Dorothy snuck along for the ride.
- 被困在了里面 - 对
- and got stuck there. - Right.
在鲍姆救了克莱夫之后
And then after Baum rescued Clive,
克莱夫回来退休了
Clive came back and retired.
做记录者能退休吗
You can retire from the Men of Letters?
显然 他们把他安置在
Well, apparently, they put him in some sort of,
类似证人保护计划下了
like, uh, witness-relocation program.
他到哪去了
Where did he end up?
我们来查清楚
Let's find out.
普雷斯利先生
Mr. Presley?
是的 是我
Yes. Yeah. Hi.
实际上 我…
Uh, actually, I'm, uh, you know,
正入神欣赏这篇…
really into this article on, uh…
关于乳房X线照片的文章
…mammograms.
非常吸引人 如果其他人想去
Riveting stuff. If somebody else wants to go…
好吧 好吧
Right. Yes. Okay.
来吧
Well…let's do this.
这位是普雷斯利先生
Mr. Presley for you, sir.
今天没别人了吗
Is that it for the day?
- 是的 先生 - 好 你可以走了
- Yes, sir. - Okay. You can head out.
把我的干洗衣物送去湖边小屋
Uh, I need my, uh, dry cleaning taken to the lake house,
接上佩珀
and, uh, pick up Pepper.
把她送去宠物美容师那里 好吗
and take her to the dog groomers, okay?
- 好的 - 谢谢
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
普雷斯利先生
Mr. Presley.
罗素·惠灵顿 请坐
Russell Wellington. Please have a seat.
那么
So…
你能不能告诉我你今天要找什么
What can you tell me about what you're looking for today?
嗯 这个嘛
Uh, right. Well, um…
让我描述一下我的梦想住宅
Let me describe my dream home.
记录者给了克莱夫一个新名字 新家
The Men of Letters gave Clive a new name, a new house,
这两个现在都还在记录中
both of which are still listed.
我觉得克莱夫可能还活着
I think Clive might be still alive.
那他差不多 得有100多岁吧
Y… well, he'd be, like, 100-something.
奥兹国的时间不一样
Time passes differently in Oz.
就在附近 我们去看看
It's close by. Let's go look.
如果他还活着 他是唯一一个
If he's still kicking, he is the only person.
有可能修好奥兹国钥匙的人
who might be able to fix the key to Oz.
- 好吧 我们走 - 好
- All right, let's go. - Okay.
我不是说我必须要按摩浴缸
I'm not saying that I have to have a jacuzzi.
我只是说我真的很喜欢泡泡
I'm just saying that I really like bubbles.
普雷斯利先生
Uh, Mr. Presley,
我要打断你
look, I'm just gonna stop you right there.
从你廉价的鞋子和褪色的牛仔裤来看
Judging from your cheap shoes and your faded jeans,
我猜你唯一
I'm guessing the only house.
有意购买的房子是带轮子的
you're in the market for comes with wheels.
听着 我很忙
Now, look, I'm a busy man.
我的时间非常宝贵
My time is extremely valuable.
我不想让乡巴佬浪费我的时间
I prefer not to have it wasted by some hayseed.
你想卖我就想买
I'm willing to buy if you're willing to sell.
不如你给我看看你有什么
So why don't you show me what you got?
我可以带你去门口
Well, I can show you the door.
你以为自己是谁
Who the hell do you think you are?
我是要救你命的人
I'm the guy who's gonna save your life.
你说什么
Excuse me?
希尔橡树街
Hill and Oak Street.
旅行车 里面有一男一女
Station wagon with a man and a woman in it,
正赶去接参加睡衣派对的小女儿
on their way to pick up their little daughter from a slumber party.
想起来了吗
That ring a bell?
我不知道你在说什么
I-I-I-I don't know what you're talking about.
不 你不知道 因为你喝得太醉
Oh, no, you wouldn't, 'cause you were too drunk.
不记得那晚任何事情
to remember anything that night.
我觉得你把我当成别人了
I think you have me confused with somebody else.
或许是个在乎的人
Or somebody that cares.
或许是个不会
Or maybe somebody who wouldn't.
花钱让别人掩饰过失杀人的人
pay people off to cover up manslaughter.
你疯了
You're insane.
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
待在这里
Stay here.
不要离开这房间
Do not leave this room.
查理
Charlie?
我们谈谈
Let's talk about this.
你们温彻斯特兄弟和你们的谈话
You Winchester boys and your talk.
废话空话 被压抑的感情
Blah, blah, blah, repressed feelings.
等等等等 被动攻击
Blah, blah, blah, passive aggression.
别这样 丫头 你不想这么做
Come on, kiddo. You don't want to do this.
我不想伤害他
I don't want to hurt him.
我只是想跟他聊聊
I just want to talk.
是啊 就像你和其他人那样聊
Yeah, like you talked to all the others?
你说得对
You're right.
我失控了
I got out of hand.
但这从来和复仇无关
But this was never about revenge.
对
Right.
我想让他看到我的脸
I want him to see my face.
我想让他看到他对我 对我们
I want him to see what he did to me…
做了什么
to us.
仅此而已
That's all.
拜托 迪恩
Please, Dean.
这是我应得的
I deserve that.
然后我们把他交给警察
And then we hand him over to the cops.
好
Okay.
先生
Mr. …
西莱斯特
Celeste.
已经很久很久没人这么叫我了
No one's called me that in a long, long time.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
我所做的…
What I did … it…
我那时太年轻 太蠢
I was young. I was stupid.
我所夺走的 我…
What I took, I…
我永远都无法补偿你
I can never give back to you.
但我在事故之后所做的事
But what I did after the accident,
真是万万不该
that never should have happened.
我没有喝醉
And I wasn't drunk for that.
我那时完全清醒
I was stone-cold sober.
那是自私
It was selfish…
是错误的
and wrong.
我该为此付出代价
And I should pay for it.
我会为此付出代价
And I will pay for it.
你夺走了我的一切
You took everything from me.
求你了
Please…
西莱斯特 我很抱歉
Celeste, I am so sorry.
罗素
Russell?
我原谅你
I forgive you.
什…
Wh…
查理
Charlie!
不要这么做 查理
Don't do this, Charlie!
迪恩
Dean.
等下 我开免提
Hey, hold on. I'm putting you on speaker.
怎么了
What happened?
结束了
It's over.
「结束了」什么意思
What do you mean, "It's over"?
她找到了罗素 杀了他
She got to Russell. She killed him.
我的天
Oh, my God.
查理 如果你能听到 我很抱歉
Charlie, if you can hear me, I'm so sorry.
这不是你的错 是我的
It's not your fault. It's mine.
不不 别这么说 这不怪你
No, no, no. Don't … don't say that. This is not on you.
好吧 我们还是尽量按计划进行 各位
All right, let's, uh … let's try and stick to the plan, guys.
你们找到办法回奥兹国了吗
Did you guys find a way back to Oz?
也许
Maybe.
第一个找到钥匙的记录者
Uh, look, t-the Man of Letters who originally found the key …
还活着
he's still alive.
他以迈克尔·卡特尔的名字住在强克逊城
He lives in Junction City under the name Michael Carter.
我把地址发你 来和我们汇合
I'll text you the address. Just come meet us.
好 我这就来
All right. I'm on my way.
你要一晚上都瞪着那玩意吗
Are you gonna stare at that all night?
我想慢慢来
I'm pacing myself.
她好可爱
She's cute.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
你骗了自己
You lied to yourself.
你就是这样
That's kind of your move.
不过你有点不对 不是吗
Something's off about you, though, isn't it?
你们总是有情况
It's always something with you boys.
我犯过错误 但我会付出代价
I've made mistakes. But I'll pay for mine.
你也会付出代价的
And you'll pay for yours.
得了吧 迪恩
Come on, Dean.
我不是禽兽 他才是
I'm not the monster here. He was.
他罪有应得
He got what he deserved.
你知道我没错
You know I'm right.
你知道变黑暗让我发现了什么吗
You know what I learned about being dark?
这让你自由
It sets you free.
你内心也知道我没说错
And part of you knows that's right, too.
你们好
Hello?
克莱夫·狄龙
Clive Dillon?
不 我的名字是
No. My name is …
迈克尔·卡特尔 对
Michael Carter, right.
但之前是克莱夫·狄龙 不是吗
But it was Clive Dillon, wasn't it?
还在做记录者时 在奥兹国时
Back in the Men of Letters? Back in Oz?
你们似乎搞错了
You seem to be confused.
这里没什么克莱夫·狄龙
There's no Clive Dillon here.
奥兹国
And Oz?
那只是童话故事
That's just a fairy tale.
应该留在书架上的童话书
It's best left on the bookshelves where it belongs.
那你从没见过这个
So you've never seen this before?
请享用
Enjoy.
秀色可餐
Delicious.
行了 听好了 黑暗查理
All right, listen, dark Charlie.
成熟点吧
Oh, grow up.
没有对错
There's no right. There's no wrong.
只有我们和他们
There's just us… And them.
是啊 没多久就不会再有你了
Yeah, well, there's not gonna be a you for very much longer.
小公主的我 是不是找到办法回奥兹国了
Did princess me find a way back to Oz?
是的
That's right.
是的 一个退休了的记录者
Yeah, a former Man of Letters, retired,
住在格兰镇 再过去两个镇就是
in Grantville, two towns over.
他们会修好通往奥兹国的钥匙 找到巫师
They're gonna fix the key to Oz, find the wizard,
把你送回你该待的地方
and put you back to where you belong.
回到查理身体里
Back into Charlie?
我该在那里吗
Is that where I belong?
这个嘛
Well…
我们走着瞧吧
Hm. We'll just see, won't we?
在此期间
In the meantime…
如果你不请她跳舞
…if you're not gonna ask her to dance,
那我就去了
then I will.
怎么了 我的朋友三振出局了吗
What happened, did my friend strike out?
你的朋友
Your friend?
她刚刚从后门离开了
She just left out the back door.
不不不
No, no, no, no!
你这个混蛋丫头
Oh, you son of a bitch!
该死的
Damn it.
萨姆
Sam.
你在哪
Hey. Where the hell are you?
混蛋查理刚刚偷走了我的宝贝
Dick Charlie just hot-wired baby.
她以为她是去找你们了
She thinks she's on her way to you.
什么
What?
我告诉她的是错误的镇
I told her the wrong town,
所以可能给你们争取了点时间
so I probably bought you a little time,
但是 注意点
but, uh, just be on the lookout.
我一搞到车就尽快去
I'll be there as soon as I can jack a ride.
谢了 快点
Thanks. Hurry.
有六把用奥兹国钢铁锻造的钥匙
The six keys of Oz were forged from Oz steel.
只能在那片魔法领域被修复
They can only be repaired in that magical realm.
所以没有办法回去
So there's no going back?
我没法把我的黑暗面关起来
I can't put my darkness away?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你在奥兹国发生了什么
What happened to you in Oz?
都在报告里
It's in my report.
报告里就说你被绑架了
Your report just said you were kidnapped.
被谁
By whom?
坏人
Bad people.
我知道这表情
I know that look.
你在说谎
You're lying.
- 说谎是… - 不好的
- And lying is … - Bad.
我知道
Yes, I know.
你所遭遇的事 亲爱的 我也遇到了
What happened to you, my dear, happened to me.
什么
What?
一群巫师抓住了我
A coven of witches grabbed me.
他们在我身上使用了内心钥 释放了黑暗
They used the inner key on me, unleashed my ID.
他很可怕
He was awful.
杀死了所有的巫师 大发脾气
He killed all the witches and went into a tantrum.
渴望权力 很疯狂
Was power-hungry, crazy.
他变成了奥兹国巫师
He became the wizard of Oz.
弗兰克的女儿 桃乐西 现在掌管翡翠城
Frank's daughter, Dorothy, runs Emerald City now.
巫师 黑暗的你 他就在她身边
The wizard, dark you, he is right by her side.
如果她有麻烦
If … if … if she's in trouble …
没有回到奥兹国的钥匙
Well, without the key to Oz,
我们就没办法回到巫师那里
there's no way we can get back to the wizard.
但是
But…
也许还有一个办法
There may well be a way…
能把他召唤来
to summon him here.
如果我受到了致命的伤
If I am mortally wounded,
他将不得不回到这里拯救我们二人
he'll have to come back here to save us both.
等等 一定还有别的办法
Wait, wait, wait. There has to be another way.
他所做的事都是我的错
What he has done is my fault.
毕竟 他是我 我是他 所以…
After all, he is me, and I am him, so…
也许我们俩该为我们的罪恶付出代价了
Maybe it's time that both of us answered for our sins.
这是件好事 对吗
It's the good thing to do, right?
对吗
Right?
我猜到你会给我假地址
I figured you'd lie about where to go to next.
换我我就会这么做
That's what I would do.
你到底想要什么
What the hell do you want?
我只想和她谈谈
I just want to talk to her.
你别想接近她
Oh, you're not going anywhere near her.
我不会让你腐蚀她
I'm not gonna let you corrupt her.
腐蚀她
Corrupt her?
你再靠近一步 我就放倒你
You take one more step, I'm gonna put you down.
我就爱这样的迪恩
There's the Dean I love.
你干了什么 你个白痴
What have you done, you fool?
你只有一个任务 活下去
You had but one task … stay alive.
而你连这个都办不到
And you couldn't even manage that.
你出拳就像个不会打架的小女生一样
You hit like a girl who never learned how to hit.
就是这样 大个子 发泄出来
That's it, big boy. Let it all out.
停下来 拜托了
Stop this, please!
让我帮帮我的朋友
Let me help my friend.
你的朋友想当个英雄
Your friend wanted to be a hero.
你知道英雄会有什么下场吗
And you know what happens to heroes?
他们都死了
They die.
你伤害了我的朋友
You hurt my friend.
我是和你学的
I learned it by watching you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
我们都原谅你了
We both do.
查理 坚持住
Charlie, hang on.
你没事吧
Hey, you okay?
迪恩 迪恩
Dean! Dean!
你做到了 是不是
You did it, didn't you?
你杀了那个巫师
You killed the wizard.
我就知道
I knew it.
你体内一直都有魔力
The magic was in you all the time.
西莱斯特
Celeste.
查理
Charlie.
查理 我在这儿呢 没事了
Charlie. Hey. I got you. It's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
没错 他…好多了
Yeah, he's, uh, he's better.
他现在平静下来了
I mean, he's calmed down now.
小卡 我们得…
Cass, we got to …
我们得找到该隐 或者…
we got to find Cain, or…
我们得找个办法
we got to find something, you know?
没错
Right.
好的 我知道 好的
Yeah, I know. I hear you. Okay.
好的 知道了 谢了
You got it. Yeah. All right. Thanks.
你不是应该休息一下吗
Shouldn't you be resting up?
我想连着睡两天应该够了吧
I think sleeping for two days in a row is probably enough.
那么…你…
So…are you…
好的 还是坏的
Good? Bad?
我想平衡我就满足了
I think I'll just settle for balanced.
关于血印有什么发现吗
Anything about the Mark?
也许 我找到了本书
Yeah, maybe. I found this book.
是一本传说 《诅咒之书》
It's a lore book … "The Book of the Damned."
听起来蛮靠谱的
Sounds legit.
在托斯卡纳的一栋图书馆里
It's in a library somewhere in Tuscany.
可能什么也查不到 不过我想着…
It might be a dead end, but I figured…
我去查查
I'll go check it out.
听着 我没法回奥兹了
Look, there's no going back to Oz.
而且巫师已经死了 桃乐西会好好的
And with the wizard gone, Dorothy will be fine.
那么你不能再冒险了吗
So, does this mean no more adventure?
我想这儿的冒险就足够我们忙活了
I think we have all the adventure we can handle right here.
那…
What about …
黑暗查理
Dark Charlie?
她…
She's, uh…
很安静
Quiet.
我得继续前进了
I just got to keep moving forward.
我们都要这样
We all do.
查理 我…
Charlie, I…
我们要解决这件事
We are going to fix this.
我不能让发生在我身上的事也发生在你身上
I'm not letting what happened to me happen to you.
但是已经发生了
But it's already happened.
- 该隐找到了办法 - 没错
- Cain found a way to live with it. - Right.
在经历了几个世纪的杀人之后
Yeah, after centuries of murder.
是的 但是
Yeah, well,
有一样东西你有他没有
there's one thing that you have that he didn't.
你是个温彻斯特
You're a Winchester.
我原谅你了 迪恩
I forgive you, Dean.
是吗 但是我没有
Yeah, well, I don't.
我知道
I know.
你就这样
It's kind of your move.
这对你有好处吗
How's that working out for you, huh?
我很抱歉 丫头
I'm so sorry, kiddo.
那就证明给我看
Then prove it.
在外头小心点
Be careful out there.
这听起来像我的性格吗
Does that sound like either of me?
假如我有所发现 我会打电话的
If I find something, I'll call.
假如没有…
If not…
我会一直找下去
I'll just keep digging.
查理 谢谢你
Charlie, thank you.
回头见 贱人们
Arrivederci, bitches.
你还好吧
You good?
不好
No.
她说得没错 迪恩
She's right, Dean.
你能做到的
You can do this.
我们能做到的
We can do this.
那我们开始吧
Then let's get to work.